Guide to the Department of Germanic Languages, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Department of Germanic Languages, Yale University, records
1929-1989
RU 218
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
24
The records consist of correspondence, budgets and appointments, course records, freshmen placement records, and student papers documenting the activities and operations of the Yale Department of Germanic Languages.
Yale University. Department of Germanic Languages
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 14-B (YRG 14-B), Records of academic departments and programs of the Yale Faculty of Arts and Sciences.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is partially restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of correspondence, budgets and appointments, course records, freshmen placement records, and student papers documenting the activities and operations of the Yale Department of Germanic Languages.
Germanic languages -- Study and teaching; Universities and colleges -- Administration; Universities and colleges -- Departments; Yale University -- Administration; Yale University -- Curricula; Yale University -- Faculty; Yale University -- Students; Yale University. Department of Germanic Languages
- Records, circa 1929-1989; Accession 1990-A-122
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2024
  - Correspondence, 1968 September - 1972 August
    - III.1.0 Purchase of Books, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - 1.2 Telephone, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - 1.3 Alterations and Equipment, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - 1.4 Travel Expenses, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - 1.5 Yale Faculty Club, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - 1.6 Office Machines Maintenance Contracts, 1968-1970 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - 2.0 Office of the Council of Masters, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - 2.1 Dean's Offices, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - 2.2 Secretary's Office, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - 2.3 Space Allocation, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - 2.5 Computer Center, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - 2.6 Language Lab and Audio-Visual, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 2.7 International Office, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - 2.9 Committee on Humanities (Pierson), 1968 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 2.10 Comptroller's Office, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - 2.13 Office of Educational Research, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 2.15 Employee Office, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - 2.16 Miscellaneous Departments, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - 2.18 Faculty Research Grant, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - 2.19 Director of Graduate Studies, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 2.20 Concilium on International and Area Studies, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - 2.21 Language Committee, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - 2.22 Coeducation, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - 2.23 Ad Hoc Committee on the Teacher Training Program, undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - 3.0 German 18, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - 3.1 Courses. general, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - 3.3 Course of Studies Committee, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - 3.4 Yale College general statistics, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - 3.5 Election and Enrollment Statistics, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - 3.6 Grading, general, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - 3.8 Faculty Committee on Teaching, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - 3.9 Grievance Committee, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - 3.10 Textbooks, Yale Co-op, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - 3.11 College Seminars, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - 4.1 Teaching Assignments, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - 4.2 White Pamphlet, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - 4.3 Bursary Students, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - 4.4 Departmental Examinations and Proctoring, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - 4.6 Junior Year Abroad, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - 4.7 German Majors, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - 4.9 Co-education, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - IV.1.3 Circulars, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - 1.4 Tutors, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - 1.6 Journal Entries, Monatshefte, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - 1.7 Magazines, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - 2.1 Graduate Courses, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - 2.2 Dutch Course, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - 2.3 Scandinavian Course, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - 2.4 Graduate Reading Course, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - 2.5 Summer Language Institute, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - 2.7 Language Laboratory, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - 2.8 MAT Program, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - 3.1 Cocktail Party, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - 3.2 Lecturers and Visitors, general, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - 3.4 Woodward Lecturers Records, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - 3.7 Film Showings and Art Exhibition, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - 3.9 Special Events, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - 3.10 Graduate Students Meetings with Counterparts, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - 4.0 Job Applications, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - 4.2 Vacancies Elsewhere, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 60)
    - V.1.0 Books, Gifts, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 61)
    - 1.1 Palmer-Schreiber, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 62)
    - 1.3 Beinecke, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 63)
    - 1.4 Branford Reading Room, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 64)
    - 1.5 Teacher's Library, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 65)
    - 1.6 Sterling Library, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 66)
    - 2.1 German Consulate, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 67)
    - 2.2 Austrian Consulate, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 68)
    - 2.3 Swiss Consulate, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 69)
    - 3.1 AATG, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 70)
    - 3.2 Goethe Society. NY, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 71)
    - 3.3 MLA- Modern Language Association, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 72)
    - 3.4 Northeastern Conference, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 73)
    - 3.5 Princeton Exam Board, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 74)
    - 3.6 TAP (Teaching Aid Project. National Carl Schurz Assoc., Inc.), 1968 (Box 1, Folder 75)
    - 3.7 ADFL, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 76)
    - 4.1 Fellowships. general, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 77)
    - 4.1.1 Morse Fellowships, 1968-1970 (Box 1, Folder 78)
    - 4.1.2 Summer Fellowships, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 79)
    - 4.1.7 Fulbright Fellowships, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 80)
    - 4.1.8 Carnegie Fellowships, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 81)
    - 4.2 Scott Prize, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 82)
    - 4.3 Book Prizes, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 83)
    - 4.6 Moore Fund, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 84)
    - 5.1 DAAD (Deutscher Akademischer Austauschdienst), 1968 (Box 1, Folder 85)
    - Lufthansa, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 86)
    - German Reading Room, undated (Box 1, Folder 87)
    - IV.4.2 Vacancies Elsewhere, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 88)
    - 4.0 Job Applications, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 89)
    - Job Opportunities, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 90)
    - 3.9 Special Events. current year, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 91)
    - V.4.2 Scott Prize, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 92)
    - 4.1.1 Morse Fellowships, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 93)
    - 4.1.2 Summer Fellowships, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 94)
    - 4.1.3 Senior Fellowships, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 95)
    - 4.1.7 Fulbright, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 96)
    - 4.4 Yale Funds, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 97)
    - 4.6 Moore Fund, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 98)
    - 5.1 DAAD, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 99)
    - IV.4.2 Vacancies Elsewhere, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 100)
    - 4.0 Job Applications, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 101)
    - Departmental Circular Letters, 1967-1978 (Box 2, Folder 102)
    - III.1.1 Books, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 103)
    - 1.3 Alterations/Equipment, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 104)
    - 1.4 Travel Expenses, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 105)
    - 1.6 Office Machine Maintenance Contracts, 1971-1973 (Box 2, Folder 106)
    - 2.0 Office of the Council of Masters, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 107)
    - 2.1 Dean Yale College/Dean Graduate School, 1970-1972 (Box 2, Folder 108)
    - 2.2 Secretary's Office, 1971-1973 (Box 2, Folder 109)
    - 2.3 Space Allocation, 1971-1973 (Box 2, Folder 110)
    - 2.4 Housing Bureau, 1970-1972 (Box 2, Folder 111)
    - 2.5 Computer Center, 1970-1972 (Box 2, Folder 112)
    - 2.6 Language Lab/Audiovisual Center, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 113)
    - 2.7 International Office/Immigration Information, 1970--1972 (Box 2, Folder 114)
    - 2.10 Comptroller's Office, 1970-1972 (Box 2, Folder 115)
    - 2.13 Office of Educational Research, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 116)
    - 2.15 Personnel Office, 1970-1972 (Box 2, Folder 117)
    - 2.16 Miscellaneous Departments, 1970-1972 (Box 2, Folder 118)
    - 2.18 Faculty Research Grant, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 119)
    - 2.19 Director of Graduate Studies, 1970-1972 (Box 2, Folder 120)
    - 2.20 Concilium on International Studies, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 121)
    - III.2.22 Coeducation, 1970-1972 (Box 2, Folder 122)
    - 3.0 German 15, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 123)
    - 3.1 Courses, general (reports, descriptions), 1970--1973 (Box 2, Folder 124)
    - 3.2 Course Curricular Discussions, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 125)
    - 3.3 Course of Studies Committee, 1970-1973 (Box 2, Folder 126)
    - 3.4 Yale College, 1970-1972 (Box 2, Folder 127)
    - 3.5 Election and Enrollment Statistics, 1970-1972 (Box 2, Folder 128)
    - 3.6 Grading, general, 1970-1972 (Box 2, Folder 129)
    - 3.7 Student's Committee on Teaching (SAB), 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 130)
    - 3.8 Faculty Committee on Teaching, 1970-1972 (Box 2, Folder 131)
    - 3.10 Yale Co-op Textbooks, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 132)
    - 4.3 Bursary Students, 1971-1973 (Box 2, Folder 133)
    - 4.4 Departmental Examinations and Proctoring, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 134)
    - 4.6 Junior Year Abroad, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 135)
    - 4.7 Majors/Literature Majors, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 136)
    - 4.9 Coeducation, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 137)
    - IV.1.1 Directories, rosters, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 138)
    - 1.3 Circulars, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 139)
    - 1.4 Tutors, 1970-1972 (Box 2, Folder 140)
    - IV.1.6 Monatshefte/other Journal Entries, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 141)
    - 2.1 Graduate Courses, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 142)
    - 2.5 Summer Language Institute, 1970-1973 (Box 2, Folder 143)
    - 3.1 Cocktail Party, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 144)
    - 3.2 Lecturers and Visitors, 1970-1972 (Box 2, Folder 145)
    - 3.4 Woodward Lecturers Records, 1970-1972 (Box 2, Folder 146)
    - 3.9 Special Events. Current Year, 1970-1972 (Box 2, Folder 147)
    - 3.10 Graduate Students Meeting with Counterparts, undated (Box 2, Folder 148)
    - 4.0 Job Applications, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 149)
    - 4.1 General Inquiries, 1970-1972 (Box 2, Folder 150)
    - 4.1 General Inquiries, 1968-1970 (Box 2, Folder 151)
    - 4.2 Vacancies Elsewhere, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 152)
    - 4.5 Opportunities abroad, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 153)
    - V.1.O Gifts, Books, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 154)
    - 1.1 Palmer-Schreiber, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 155)
    - 1.2 Seminar, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 156)
    - 1.3 Beinecke, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 157)
    - 1.4 Branford Reading Room, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 158)
    - 1.5 Teacher's Library, undated (Box 2, Folder 159)
    - 1.6 Sterling, 1970-1972 (Box 2, Folder 160)
    - 2. 1 German, 1970-1972 (Box 2, Folder 161)
    - 2.2 Austrian, 1970-1972 (Box 2, Folder 162)
    - 3.1 AATG, 1970-1972 (Box 2, Folder 163)
    - 3.3 HLA, 1970-1972 (Box 2, Folder 164)
    - 3.4 Northeastern Conference/AP Conference, 1970-1972 (Box 2, Folder 165)
    - 3.7 Actel. NY, 1970-1972 (Box 2, Folder 166)
    - 4.1 Fellowships. general/Lectureships, 1970-1972 (Box 2, Folder 167)
    - ABLAGE, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 168)
    - Reform of German IS, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 169)
    - 111.1.1 Purchases Administration, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 170)
    - 1.3 Monthly Statements, undated (Box 2, Folder 171)
    - 1.4 Telephone, 1965-1968 (Box 2, Folder 172)
    - 1.5 Alterations and Equipment, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 173)
    - 1.6 Travel Expenses, 1959-1963 (Box 2, Folder 174)
    - 1.7 Non-Budget Expenses, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 175)
    - 1.8 Yale Faculty Club, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 176)
    - 2.0 Office of the Council of Masters, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 177)
    - 2.1 Correspondence with the Deans, 1964-1968 (Box 2, Folder 178)
    - 2.2 Correspondence with the Secretary's Office, 1966-1968 (Box 2, Folder 179)
    - 2.3 Space Allocation, 1966-1968 (Box 2, Folder 180)
    - 2.4 Housing Bureau, 1963-1968 (Box 2, Folder 181)
    - 2.5 Computer Center, 1966-1968 (Box 2, Folder 182)
    - 2.6 Language Lab and Audiovisual Center, 1959-1968 (Box 2, Folder 183)
    - 2.7 International Office, 1965-1968 (Box 2, Folder 184)
    - 2.8 Yale University Council, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 185)
    - 2.9 Committee on the Humanities (Pierson), 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 186)
    - 2.10 Comptroller's Office, 1966-1968 (Box 2, Folder 187)
    - 2.11 Yale Art Gallery, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 188)
    - 2.12 Yale Travel Office, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 189)
    - 2.13 Educational Research Office, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 190)
    - 2.14 Safety Policy andSafety Organization, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 191)
    - 2.15 Employee Office, 1966-1968 (Box 2, Folder 192)
    - 2.16 Miscellaneous Departments, 1966-1968 (Box 2, Folder 193)
    - 2.17 Yale Literary Group, 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 194)
    - 2.18 Faculty Research Grants, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 195)
    - 3.1 Undergraduate Courses, general, 1965-1968 (Box 3, Folder 196)
    - 3.2 Course Curricular Changes and Discussion, 1955-1968 (Box 3, Folder 197)
    - 3.3 Course of Study Committee, 1963-1968 (Box 3, Folder 198)
    - 3.9 Grievance C.ornmittee, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 199)
    - 4.1 Teaching Assignments, 1965-1968 (Box 3, Folder 200)
    - 4.2 White Pamphlet, 1965-1968 (Box 3, Folder 201)
    - 4.3 Bursary Students, 1961-1967 (Box 3, Folder 202)
    - 4.4 Departmental Exams, 1955-1968 (Box 3, Folder 203)
    - 4.5 Advanced Placement, 1957-1965 (Box 3, Folder 204)
    - 4.6 Junior Year Abroad, 1960-1967 (Box 3, Folder 205)
    - 4.6 Junior Year Abroad, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 206)
    - 4.7 German Majors, 1957-1967 (Box 3, Folder 207)
    - 4.8 Special Majors, 1965-1967 (Box 3, Folder 208)
    - 3.4 Yale College General Statistics, 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 209)
    - 3.5 Election and Enrollment, 1961-1968 (Box 3, Folder 210)
    - 3.6 Grading. general, 1963-1965 (Box 3, Folder 211)
    - 3.7 Student Committee on Teaching, 1966-1968 (Box 3, Folder 212)
    - 3.8 Faculty Committee on Teaching, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 213)
    - 3.10 Vassar-Yale, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 214)
    - IV.1.1 Directories, Rosters etc., 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 215)
    - 1.2 Faculty Offices, 1864-1965 (Box 3, Folder 216)
    - 1.3 Circulars, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 217)
    - 1.4 Tutors. etc., undated (Box 3, Folder 218)
    - 1.5 Departmental Consultants and Placement, 1963-1967 (Box 3, Folder 219)
    - 1.6 Journal Entries, 1964-1968 (Box 3, Folder 220)
    - 1.7 Zeitschriften, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 221)
    - 2.0 Committee on Graduate Instruction in German Literature, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 222)
    - 2.1 Graduate Course Offerings, 1963-1968 (Box 3, Folder 223)
    - 2.2 Dutch Course, 1963-1964 (Box 3, Folder 224)
    - 2.3 Scandanavian Course, 1961-1968 (Box 3, Folder 225)
    - 2.4 Graduate Reading Course, 1964-1966 (Box 3, Folder 226)
    - 2.5 Summer Language Institute, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 227)
    - 2.6 Linguistics, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 228)
    - 2.7 Language Lab, 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 229)
    - 3.0 German 15, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 230)
    - 3.1 Cocktail Party, 1964-1968 (Box 3, Folder 231)
    - 3.2.1 Accepted Lecturers -Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 232)
    - 3.2 Lecturers and Visitors, general, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 233)
    - 3.3 Woodward_Lecturers Record, 1-966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 234)
    - 3.4 Woodward Lecturers Record, 1966-1968 (Box 3, Folder 235)
    - 3.5 German Club Records, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 236)
    - 3.6 Yale German Review, 1964-1967 (Box 3, Folder 237)
    - 3.8 Syllabus, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 238)
    - 3.9 Special Events, Past Lectures, 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 239)
    - 3.10 Graduate Students Meeting with Counterparts, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 240)
    - 3.11 Departmental Play, undated (Box 3, Folder 241)
    - 4.0 Job Applications, 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 242)
    - 4.1 General Inquiries, 1966-1968 (Box 3, Folder 243)
    - 4.2 Vacancies Elsewhere, 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 244)
    - 4.3 Graduate Students Elsewhere, 1966-1968 (Box 3, Folder 245)
    - IV.4.4 Summerschools Elsewhere, 1964-1968 (Box 4, Folder 246)
    - 4.5 Opportunities Abroad, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 247)
    - V.I Libraries, general, 1962-1968 (Box 4, Folder 248)
    - 1.1 Palmer-Schreiber Library, 1962-1968 (Box 4, Folder 249)
    - 1.2 Seminar Library (lacking), undated (Box 4, Folder 250)
    - 1.3 Reinecke Library, 1963-1968 (Box 4, Folder 251)
    - 1.4 Branford Reading Room, 1963-1968 (Box 4, Folder 252)
    - 1.5 Teacher's Library, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 253)
    - 1.6 Sterling Library, 1966-1968 (Box 4, Folder 254)
    - 2. Embassies. general (locking), undated (Box 4, Folder 255)
    - 2.1 German Embassy, 1865-1968 (Box 4, Folder 256)
    - 2.2 Austrian Embassy, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 257)
    - 2.3 Swiss Embassy, 1965-1968 (Box 4, Folder 258)
    - 3. Associations, general (lacking), undated (Box 4, Folder 259)
    - 3.1 MTG, 1963-1968 (Box 4, Folder 260)
    - 3.2 Goethe Society, 1965-1968 (Box 4, Folder 261)
    - 3.3 MLA, 1966-1967 (Box 4, Folder 262)
    - 3.4 The Northeastern Conference (on Foreign Language), 1967 (Box 4, Folder 263)
    - 3.5 Princeton Exam Board, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 264)
    - 3.6 TAP - Teaching Aid Project, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 265)
    - 3.7 American Committee for the Study of Austrian Literature, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 266)
    - 4.1 Gifts, Funds. Prizes, Fellowships (general), 1964-1968 (Box 4, Folder 267)
    - 4.1.1 morse Fellowship, 1953-1967 (Box 4, Folder 268)
    - 4.1.2 Summer Fellowship, 1965-1968 (Box 4, Folder 269)
    - 4.1.3 Senior Faculty Fellowships, 1958-1967 (Box 4, Folder 270)
    - 4.1.4 College Fellowship, 1963-1966 (Box 4, Folder 271)
    - 4.1.5 German Universities Fellowship, 1960-1964 (Box 4, Folder 272)
    - 4.1.6 NDEA Fellowships, 1965-1967 (Box 4, Folder 273)
    - 4.1.7 Fulbright Fellowships (lacking), undated (Box 4, Folder 274)
    - 4.1.8 Carnegie Teaching Fellowship, 1966-1967 (Box 4, Folder 275)
    - 4.1.9 Woodrow Wilson National Fellowship, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 276)
    - 4.2 Scott Prize, general, 1961-1968 (Box 4, Folder 277)
    - 4.3 Book Prize, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 278)
    - 4.4 Yale Funds, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 279)
    - 4.5 Honorary Degrees, 1964-1966 (Box 4, Folder 280)
    - 5.1 DAAD, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 281)
    - IV.4.2 Vacancies Elsewhere, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 282)
    - Native Speakers, Directions for, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 283)
    - Hans Henry Jahnn, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 284)
    - Pinthus. K., 1956-1958 (Box 4, Folder 285)
    - Till. Miss Christine, 1946-1956 (Box 4, Folder 286)
    - White Pamphlet, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 287)
    - 111.3.1.3 Graduate Reading Course, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 288)
    - 3.4 General Administration, 1964-1965 (Box 4, Folder 289)
    - 3.4 General Administrative Procedures, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 290)
    - 3.4 Prof. Bluhm. Departmental, 1961-1963 (Box 4, Folder 291)
    - 3.7 Yale Stationery Purchases -Current Requisitions, 1956-1963 (Box 4, Folder 292)
    - 1961-1963 (Box 4, Folder 293)
    - 1964-1965 (Box 4, Folder 294)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 295)
    - 3.7.1 Purchases -Monthly Statements, 1964-1965 (Box 4, Folder 296)
    - 3.7.1 Purchases -Monthly Statements, 1965-1966 (Box 4, Folder 297)
    - 3.8 Telephones, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 298)
    - 3.8 Telephones, general, 1964-1965 (Box 4, Folder 299)
    - 3.8.1 Telephones -Statements, 1962-1963 (Box 4, Folder 300)
    - 3.8.1 Telephones -Monthly Statements, 1964-1965 (Box 4, Folder 301)
    - 3.12 Faculty Offices, 1957-1964 (Box 4, Folder 302)
    - 3.13 Departmental Meetings, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 303)
    - 3.13 Departmental Meetings -Minutes, 1964-1965 (Box 4, Folder 304)
    - 3.13 Departmental Meetings-Minutes, 1965-1966 (Box 4, Folder 305)
    - 3.15 Gifts, 1958-1964 (Box 4, Folder 306)
    - 3.16 Fellowships. general, 1964-1968 (Box 4, Folder 307)
    - 3. 16 Fellowships. general, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 308)
    - 3.16.1 Summer Fellowships, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 309)
    - 3.19 Austrian Consulates Correspondence, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 310)
    - 3.19 Austrian Consul, 1953-1967 (Box 4, Folder 311)
    - 3.19 Deutsche Bot3chaft, Washington, 1955-1963 (Box 4, Folder 312)
    - 3.19 German Consulate. Boston, 1959-1963 (Box 4, Folder 313)
    - 3.19 Embassies, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 314)
    - 3.20 Summer Programmes, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 315)
    - 3.23 Summer Language Institute - Yale
      - 1957-1960 (Box 4, Folder 316)
      - 1961 (Box 4, Folder 317)
      - 1962 (Box 4, Folder 318)
      - 1963 (Box 4, Folder 319)
      - 1965-1966 (Box 4, Folder 320)
    - 4.1. 1 German Club -Records, 1963-1965 (Box 4, Folder 321)
    - 4.3 Germanic Club, 1963-1965 (Box 4, Folder 322)
    - 4.3 Germanic Club -general, 1964-1965 (Box 4, Folder 323)
    - 4.3.1 Newsletters, 1955-1958 (Box 4, Folder 324)
    - 4.1 Yale German Club. general, 1963-1965 (Box 5, Folder 325)
    - 4.3 Germanic Club, general, 1963-1965 (Box 5, Folder 326)
    - 4.3.1 Germanic - Records, 1964-1966 (Box 5, Folder 327)
    - 4.3.1 Germanic - Records, 1887-1964 (Box 5, Folder 328)
    - 4.3.1 Germanic Minutes, 1934-36 (Box 5, Folder 329)
    - 4.5 Annual Department Prizes, 1963-1966 (Box 5, Folder 330)
    - 4.6 Cocktail Party, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 331)
    - 4.7 Visitors, 1964-1965 (Box 5, Folder 332)
    - 4.7 Visitors, 1965-1966 (Box 5, Folder 333)
    - 4.7 Distinguished Visitors andLecturers, 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 334)
    - 4.8 Summer Language Institute, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 335)
    - IV.3.2.1 Accepted Lecturers Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 5, Folder 336)
    - 3.19.1 Lukas Burckhardt, 1963-1965 (Box 5, Folder 337)
    - 3.23 Summer Language Institute, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 338)
    - III.1.1 Purchase of Books (lacking), undated (Box 5, Folder 339)
    - 1.2 Communication Department, 1979-1982 (Box 5, Folder 340)
    - 1.4 Office Machines Maintenance Contracts, 1980-1982 (Box 5, Folder 341)
    - 2.0 Office of the Council of Masters, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 342)
    - 2.1 Dean Yale College/Dean Graduate School, 1980-1982 (Box 5, Folder 343)
    - 2.2 Secretary's Office, 1979-1983 (Box 5, Folder 344)
    - 2.3 Office of Facilities Planning, 1979-1982 (Box 5, Folder 345)
    - 2.5 Computer Center, 1979-1982 (Box 5, Folder 346)
    - 2.8 University Council, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 347)
    - 2.9 Committee/Council/Division of the Humanities, 1979-1981 (Box 5, Folder 348)
    - 2.10 Comptroller's Office/ Finance andAdministration, 1979-1982 (Box 5, Folder 349)
    - 2.15 Personnel Office, 1979-1982 (Box 5, Folder 350)
    - 2.16 Misc. Departments and Committees, 1979-1982 (Box 5, Folder 351)
    - 2.19 Director of Graduate Studies, 1979-1982 (Box 5, Folder 352)
    - 2.19.a Director of Undergraduate Studies, 1980-1982 (Box 5, Folder 353)
    - 2.19.b Graduate School Alumni Fund Raising, 1980-1982 (Box 5, Folder 354)
    - 2.20 Concilium on International Studies, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 355)
    - 2.21 Language Committee, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 356)
    - 2.22 Committee on Communication, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 357)
    - 2.27 Chairman -GROUP, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 358)
    - 2.28 Board of Permanent Officers, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 359)
    - 3.1 Courses - general/Women's Studies, 1979-1981 (Box 5, Folder 360)
    - 3.2 Course Curricular discussions/Curricular Committee, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 361)
    - 3.3 Course of Studies Committee, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 362)
    - 3.4 Yale College, 1979-1981 (Box 5, Folder 363)
    - 3.5 Election and Enrollment Statistics, 1979-1982 (Box 5, Folder 364)
    - 3.10 Yale Co-op Textbooks, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 365)
    - 4.1 Teachlng Assignments, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 366)
    - 4.3 Bursary Students, 1979-1982 (Box 5, Folder 367)
    - 4.6 Junior Year Abroad, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 368)
    - IV.1.3 Circulars, 1980-1982 (Box 5, Folder 369)